[{"id": 1980, "question": "UNICEF reports that 40 million children below the age of 15 suffer from abuse and neglect. The USA National Committee to Prevent Child Abuse finds 3 million new reports of child abuse or neglect every year. According to such information on human rights abuses of children, the United Nations declared 2010 as the International Year of Youth. In answer to the common human rights abuses of young people, Dr. Mary Shuttleworth of Youth for Human Rights International(YHRI) recently completed her seventh annual World Tour to five continents in eighty days. The purpose of the tour is to promote the to tens of thousands of children and officials. According to UNICEF, 1.2 million children are illegally traded all over the world every year. Sold as goods, these children are forced into inhuman labor, ...\n\nQ: According to para. 2, Dr. Shuttleworth first started her annual World Tour in    _   .", "options": ["2000", "2004", "2008", "2010"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1823, "question": "Earth Day events are arranged all over the world, but for New Yorkers in the Catskill region, there are plenty of options.s6t---- Earth Day Celebrations6t---- Place: Frost Valley; Time: Friday, April 8 - Saturday, April 9 (Check-in at 5:00 pm on Friday). Activities include recycled arts and crafts projects, classes on composting and recycling, nature hikes, and a greenhouse planting project. All ages are welcomed. $15.00 per person (includes lunch). Kids 5 and under free. Call (845) 985-2291 for more details and to register.s6t---- Earth Festivals6t---- Place: Milford Central School; Time: Saturday, April 9 (11:00 am - 3:00 pm). Enjoy exhibits, activities and entertainment. Bring along your recyclables to be collected. You'll go green! Fashion Show will be held at the end of the day. Admis...\n\nQ: Where will you go if you only have time on Sunday?s6t----", "options": ["Frost Valley.s6t----", "Milford Central School.", "Grafton Lakes State Park.", "Schoharie Crossing State Historic Site.s6t----"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1348, "question": "Six seconds after its launch in Virginia, US, an unmanned rocket bound for the International Space Station (ISS) exploded, disappointing people both on Earth and in space. Hundreds of millions of dollars worth of cargo was destroyed in the Oct. 28 explosion due to An\"equipment failure\", said Orbital Sciences, the company hired by NASA for the resupply mission. The rocket was carrying a cargo ship loaded with 2,200 kilograms of supplies such as food, tools, parts, and experiments. Roughly a third of the cargo was a series of scientific investigations. Some of them were from high school students in the US. For example, 10 students from the Cristo Rey Jesuit College Preparatory School of Houston were conducting experiments about microgravity and put their samples on the rocket. \"I know that f...\n\nQ: We can conclude from the article that the situation seemed  _  for astronauts on board the ISS when the rocket exploded.", "options": ["hopeless", "interesting", "depressing", "dangerous"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1949, "question": "\"It was cool,because I got a chance to be in a studio and see how a record is made,\"says 14-year-old Javon Martin,who joined the music clubhouse 3 years ago.\"It has impacted my life in a big way. People are actually starting to see me as an artist.\"Ten-year-old Akheylah Hunter didn't play an instrument when she became a club member last year. Now,she plays piano and sings with the band. What she likes best,she says,is performing.\"We performed in different places,\"she says.\"We go on trips and it is fun.\" Since the Music Clubhouse opened three years ago,it's served almost 500 kids.Aggeler says performing in front of different audiences helps the young musicians build self-esteem.Coming to the club to prepare for those performances helps them learn how to deal with their personal problems and...\n\nQ: Which of the following was NOT mentioned as a benefit of joining the club?", "options": ["Helping the youngsters to build self-confidence.", "Helping its members escape from problems.", "Learning to deal with personal problems.", "Learning to get help from nonprofit groups."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 678, "question": "Hundreds of students from around the world gathered in New York City last week for the Microsoft Imagine Cup finals. They came to present their ideas for using technology to solve world problems. Microsoft education director Suzi Levine says the nine-year-old program began mainly as a competition to create technology. SUZI LEVINE: \"When we realized that students really actually want to have a purpose for what they're creating, we introduced the idea of inspiring them with the UN Millennium Development Goals and suggesting that they use those for their muse . \"This past year we also rolled out something called the Imagine Cup Solve This library , where IGOs, NGOs and nonprofits can submit some of the technical challenges that they would like students to consider for their solutions.\" Micros...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true ?", "options": ["The program is sponsored by Microsoft.", "Next year, the awards ceremony will be held in New York City.", "Any high school or college student can attend the finals.", "The initial purpose of the program is to solve world problems using technology."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 571, "question": "Sheep, like turkeys and ostriches, are not considered the cleverest animals. British scientists said last Wednesday human may have underestimated the woolly creatures. They could be much smarter than we think. Researchers at the Babraham Institute in Cambridge, southern. England, have shown that animals have a good memory system and are extremely good at recognizing faces--which they think is a sure sign of intelligence. Behavioral scientist Keith Kendrick and his friends trained 20 sheep to recognize and distinguish 25 pairs of sheep faces and used electrodes to measure their brain activity, which showed they could remember 50 faces for up to two years. \"If they can do that with faces, the fact is that they have to have reasonable intelligence, otherwise, what is the point of having a sys...\n\nQ: When scientists found that sheep show similar abilities in many ways to humans they may think it   _  .", "options": ["worrying", "moving", "frightening", "interesting"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2397, "question": "There's a guy like me in every state and federal prison in America,I guess--I'm the guy who can get these for you:cigarettes,a bag of cigar,if you want that,a bottle of wine to celebrate your son or daughter's high school graduation,or almost anything else...within reason,that is.It wasn't always that way. I came to Shawshank when I was just twenty,and I am one of the few people in the prison who is willing to admit what he did.I committed murder.I put a large insurance policy on my wife,who was three years older than 1 was,and then I fixed the brakes of the car her father had given us as a wedding present.It worked out exactly as I had planned,except I hadn't planned on her stopping to pick up the neighbour woman and the woman's son on the way down Castle Hill and into town.The brakes let...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE about the man?", "options": ["He regrets having committed the crime.", "He will be out of prison in the near future.", "He thinks the trial a mistake and is unfair.", "He has found out the"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2462, "question": "With a good shopping position and the right amount of money , any educated person ought to be able to make a living out of a bookshop . It is not a difficult trade to learn and the large chain-stores can never force the small bookseller out of existence as they have done to the corner shop . But the hours of work are very long-I was only doing a part-time job , but my boss put in a seventy-hour week ,besides regular journeys out of shopping hours to buy books . The real reason why I should not like to be back in the book trade for life , however , is that while I was in it, I lost my love of books . A bookseller cannot always tell the truth about his books , and that gives him a dislike for them . There was a time when I really did love books--loved the sight and smell and feel of them--if...\n\nQ: The author will only buy new books_.", "options": ["if he feels dull and tired", "after he gives up his job as a bookseller", "which are interesting but hard to borrow", "when he throws away old ones"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1711, "question": "It's a warm summer afternoon. You're cooking up the catch of the day over a campfire. Suddenly, a few raindrops fall on your arms, and before you know it, the sky is opened up. Then you hear what sounds like thunder in the distance. What should you do? Your tent is close by and would offer shelter from the pouring rain. There's a campsite picnic shelter a few minutes down the path. And then you remember that your car is parked down the road. What's your safest choice to make sure you and your families are safe? It's a common question for many hikers and campers, especially when they are camping during summer months. Heading to your car is almost always the safest choice. Your tent and a picnic shelter will keep you dry, but they offer little or no protection against lightening. Your car, o...\n\nQ: To avoid lightening in a storm, you'd better   _  .", "options": ["go into your tent quickly", "cook up the catch of the day over a campfire", "get into your car and return to your campsite", "run into a campsite picnic shelter at once"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 706, "question": "During the tsunami disaster of 2004, over 300,000 people died. No one has counted the number of animals killed, but we know that it wasn't many. All over the region, before the disaster struck, animals were behaving strangely. Shortly before the tsunami, in Khaolak, Thailand, twelve elephants that were giving tourists rides became agitated. They suddenly left their usual habitat, carrying four surprised Japanese tourists to safety. On the eastern coast of India, flamingos , which should be breeding at this time of year, suddenly flew to higher ground. Of the two thousand wild pigs that live in an Indian nature reserve, only one was found dead after the tsunami. The idea that the animals are able to predict disasters is nothing new. In fact, it has been well-recorded over the years. Twelve ...\n\nQ: The best title of the passage might be   _  .", "options": ["Few Animals Died in Tsunami", "Animals React to the Disasters", "Animals can Survive the Disasters", "Watching Animals will Save Us"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3340, "question": "(Reuters)The Thunderbird is one of the most readily recognized creatures of American Indian mythology.While the vast majority of biologists believe the Thunderbird myth to be nothing more than a spiritual symbol, some zoologists believe that the hard may actually exist. I still vividly recall seeing an impossibly large raptor when I was five years old, which a few people have said might be the Thunderbird.Standing in my grandmother's back yard in Alabama, I recall watching an enormous black bird with a swallow - like tail flying directly over me from an oak tree. Its wingspan seemed to be at least three times my height, which would have made it at least fourteen feet across. While the early childhood memory is often unreliable, I clearly remember the details of the \"Thunderbird\".To this ve...\n\nQ: What can be leant from the passage?", "options": ["Three Thunderbirds have been witnessed so far.", "The Thunderbird are similar to sea eagles in size.", "Three boys were injured by the Thunderbird in 1977.", "The huge bird left a deep impression upon the author."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1908, "question": "The ancient whistled language of the small island of La Gomera, off the coast of Africa, is about to disappear because of new technology and globalization. Now, a web company has taken on the task of saving the language by marrying history with technology. Silbo Gomero, a language used only on La Gomera Island, sounds to the untrained ear like few other known languages. The sounds that make up this language are made by whistling, rather than by speaking. The language was brought to the island by African setters many centuries ago. To communicate among the _ populated inland hills and valleys, shepherds had to use the whistled language, which could be heard and understood over distances of up to eight kilometers, compared to about 200 meters for a spoken word. With the development of new te...\n\nQ: Compared to other languages, Silbo Gomero is special because it   _  .", "options": ["has a very long story.", "was once very popular in Africa.", "doesn't use sounds", "is spoken by whistling"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 662, "question": "The woman had died when the rescuers found her after the terrible earthquake. She was covered by a destroyed house. Through gaps of those ruins,the rescuers could see her last posture . It was something like an ancient person who was kowtowing ,but it just looked strange because she was out of shape by pressure. The rescuers confirmed her death by touching her through the gaps of the ruins. They shouted at the ruins again and again,knocked the bricks using various tools,but no reply inside. Then the rescuing team went to the next building. Suddenly the leader ran back,calling \"Come here.\" He came to the body,put his hands under the woman,feeling and touching,then shouted loudly and gladly,\"There is someone,a baby,still living.\" Through some efforts,rescuers cleaned up the ruins which block...\n\nQ: When the rescuers found the mom,she    .", "options": ["was using her mobile phone to ask for help", "begged the rescuers to save her baby first", "was struggling with the pressure", "didn't have the normal shape"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3259, "question": "\"Ten years ago I could never have imagined I'd be doing this,\"says Greg Pal,33,a former software executive. \"I mean ,this is essentially agriculture ,right? But the people I talk to, especially the ones coming out of business school , think this is the one hot area everyone wants to get into .\" He means bugs. To be more accurate, the genetic change of bugs---very, very small ones---so that when they feed on agricultural waste such as woodchip or wheat straw ,they do something extraordinary . They excrete crude oil. Unbelievably ,this is not science fiction .Mr. Pal holds up a small cup of bug excretion that could ,in theory ,be poured into the tank of the big Lexus SUX next to us .Not that Mr. Pal was willing to risk it just yet .He gives it a month before the first vehicle is filled up wi...\n\nQ: To make the bugs excrete crude oil, Greg Pal has to  _", "options": ["keep them in an isolated tank", "change their genes first", "change their usual diet first", "kill them for bacteria"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3389, "question": "Little Tom down the street calls our dog \"The keep dog\".Zip is a sheep dog. But when Tom tries to say\" Seep\", it comes out \"keep\". And in a way Tom is right. Zip is always bringing things home for us to keep! I'll tell you about some of them. Zip's first present was a shoe. It was made of green silk. We didn't know how Zip found the shoe. But after a moment Mary, my big sister, told me the shoe had a strange smell. I nodded and held my nose. \"What do you think it is?\" \"It smells like something for cleaning. I think someone tried to clean a spot off the shoe. Then he put it at the door to dry.\" \"Along came Zip. And good-bye shoe!\" I said.\"We should take it back.\" \"We can't \".said my sistter. \"Maybe little Tom is right,\" Mary said. \"Maybe Zip is a keep dog!\"...\n\nQ: Tom calls Zip \"the keep dog\" because   _  .", "options": ["the dog likes keeping things", "the dog likes playing with shoes", "he doesn't know the dog's name", "he can't pronounce the word \" sheep\" well"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3476, "question": "Once upon a time, on an isolated island in the Java sea, lived short people who dominated(, ) the food chain. Standing no more than three and a half feet tall, these human ancestors hunted giant rats, lumbering lizards , and _ elephants. It sounds a bit like a fairy tale, but it's true. Unearthed relics on the island uncovered the remains of a race of tiny human ancestors. Homo floresiensis, as the newly discovered species has been named, apparently could date back to 13,000 years ago. This means they have a lot in common with modern humans. So how and why did these people get so small? Scientists suspect that it's due to the fact that this race lived on an isolated island with limited resources. Take the miniature elephants for example. When elephants first came to the island either by sw...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the fact Homo floresiensis are very small is based on  _  .", "options": ["the islanders in the Java Sea", "the human ancestors", "the unearthed relics", "a newspaper report"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 675, "question": "Ben and his wife Susan were on their way to have dinner with their friends. It was a dark,windy night, and they did not know the way very well. They drove through a town until they found what they thought was the road to Dorling,where their friends lived. But it soon became clear that they were not on the road to Dorling at all. The road that they were on was getting narrower,and there were no other cars on it. The wind was blowing harder with every minute that passed. They came to a small village .They drove past a church and then two houses without lights on. There was nobody about to tell them where they were,or where the road went. Just then,Ben saw a telephone box,twenty meters or so further on. While he walked back along the road to see if there was a name outside the church,Susan te...\n\nQ: Ben went to the church to see if there was a name outside because   _  .", "options": ["he was sure to find some people who knew Dorling", "he hoped to get help from there", "he wanted to telephone his friends where they were", "he wanted to stay there for the night"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 982, "question": "NEW DELHI, India (AP)--India is fast becoming a top destination for tourists thanks to a forceful campaign to push the country's Himalayan spas and beaches, officials say. Tourism officials have been crisscrossing the globe as part of the government's \"Incredible India\" campaign launched in 2003. And the results are beginning to show. Tourists traveling to prefix = st1 /Indiahave jumped by nearly 26 percent from last year and the number is expected to cross 3 million this year, said Amitabh Kant, chairman of the India Tourism Development Corp. \"Foreign exchange earnings, too, have shown a nearly 40 percent rise this year,\" Kant told The Associated Press. India's earnings from tourism were $4.3 billion between January and November 2004, compared to $3.1 billion for the same period of 2003. ...\n\nQ: Which of the following may NOT belong to the advantages of India?", "options": ["Hospitality.", "Cultural diversity.", "Good value for money.", "Natural scenery."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2559, "question": "You may have heard of the book Moby Dick(<<>> ), written by the American author Herman Melville. You may also know that Moby Dick is considered one of the greatest novels ever written. However, it might surprise you to find out Herman Melville was not always a highly regarded author. Melville's first two novels, Typee and Omoo, were widely read and financially successfully. They were both exciting tales of adventures at sea and experiences with people in foreign lands. Melville became quite famous. However, upon the publication of his third book, Mardi, Melville's popularity began to weaken. He was no longer interested in telling tales of pure adventure, and his writing took on a style that alienated the general reading public of his time. Melville published Moby Dick in October of 1851. i...\n\nQ: The text may be taken from  _  .", "options": ["a writing guide", "a literary journal.", "a science magazine.", "a critical book on literature."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 120, "question": "Winter is the time of year when people feel very blessed. This isn't because people feel thankful for the cold weather, nor because the important festivals---Christmas or Spring Festival---offer an excuse to celebrate. In fact, \"Bless you!\" is a common response if someone sneezes, a symptom of catching a cold or the flu. Colds and the flu are the most common illnesses of autumn and winter as the weather gets colder. Viruses cause them. If you get one you will feel annoyed, but it is not usually serious. The flu is spread from person to person when we come into contact with a person with the virus. We get the virus on our hands and then we touch our noses and our mouths. We can pass on the flu before we realize we have it. You can infect others one day before symptoms develop and for up to ...\n\nQ: We can infer the passage that  _  .", "options": ["People catch a cold or the flu only in autumn or winter.", "people getting a flu vaccination won't catch the illness for life.", "flu can cause symptoms such as sore throat and a runny nose.", "people with the virus of flu but having no symptoms can still infect others."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 905, "question": "When Charles Strattion was five, he stopped growing. His mother took him to see the famous showman, P. T. Barnum, and thought a small person would be the perfect addition to his show. He hired Charles' parents along with him, and they traveled around the world together. He gave the two-foot-tall Charles a new name, general Tom Thumb. He taught Tom how to sing, dance, act, and tell jokes. When he felt Tom was ready to perform on stage, he made up ads. To stir up great interest, he said that Tom was eleven years old and had come from England. Tom's act was very popular and brought in a lot of money. By the time Tom was an adult, he had grown very rich. He had become a billionaire at the age of twenty-five. Fortunately for Tom, Mr. Barnum added more little people to his show, and Tom became l...\n\nQ: It was very funny when Tom danced on a wooden plate held by a person who was eight feet tall because  _  .", "options": ["the wooden plate would make it sound as of Tom were tap dancing", "it made Tom feel taller", "the eight-foot-tall man was the only tall person Tom trusted", "the difference between them would make Tom look even smaller"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3215, "question": "Researchers in the psychology department at the University of California at Los Angeles (UCLA) have discovered a major difference in the way men and women respond to stress. This difference may explain why men are more likely to suffer from stress-related disorders. Until now, psychological research has maintained that both men and women have the same \"fight-or-flight\" reaction to stress. In other words, individuals either react with aggressive behavior, such as verbal or physical conflict (\"fight\"), or they react by withdrawing from the stressful situation (\"flight\"). However, the UCLA research team found that men and women have quite different biological and behavioral responses to stress. While men often react to stress in the fight-or-flight response, women often have another kind of r...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true about oxytocin according to the passage?", "options": ["Men have the same level of oxytocin as women do.", "Oxytocin used to be studied in both men and women.", "Both animals and people have high levels of oxytocin.", "Oxytocin has more of an effect on women than on men."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 659, "question": "Want to know the dynamic pulse of China's economy? Get a glance of the most important business activities taking place here every day through Business Daily Update, a service offered by China Daily information via the World Wide Web. Placed under 10 categories, over 25 news items appear each day with the top three events highlighted all in English.Business Daily Update is just a few mouse clicks away. Subscribe to BDU for an annual fee of US $240.Email and fax services are also Available upon request. For more information, please contact Business Daily Update: Tel: (010)64941107, (010) 64924488 ext.2000; Fax: +86-10-64941125 Email: bdu@chinadaily.com.cn;URL:http://www.chinadaily.com.cn/bdu...\n\nQ: To get the information from BDU every day, you must   _  .", "options": ["understand Chinese", "know something about the mouse", "know how to operate a computer", "how to use a fax machine"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3421, "question": "Hello-Hello, a creative mobile language learning company, announced the launch of Hello-Hello World, a free application for the iPad that helps people learn a new language by connecting them with native speakers through social networking. The application lets users complete language lessons and connect with Hello-Hello's global community of language learners with members in almost 100 countries to help each other in the learning process. Hello-Hello World is available in 11 different languages and allows users to submit both oral and writing exercises for their friends and Hello-Hello's language experts to review. Users are also able to provide written feedback on their friend's exercises directly from their mobile devices. \"The most effective way to learn a new language is through total i...\n\nQ: Which mobile device is Hello-Hello World being released for now?", "options": ["The iPhone.", "The ipad.", "Android.", "Blackberry."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3280, "question": "Boxing was long viewed sickly. Generally forbidden by law in earlier days, the fighting was usually done with bare fists, and matches often lasted forty or fifty rounds. In 1882 John L. Sullivan, a fighter of great power, won the world heavyweight championship from Paddy Ryan in a bare fisted battle marked by hitting, scratching, and biting without any rule. Five years later, while fighting Patsy Cardiff at Minneapolis, Sullivan broke his right arm in the third round, but he continued fighting to the sixth round and won. In 1889, Sullivan defeated Jade Kilrain with his bare fists in another championship fight, winning twenty thousand dollars and a diamond prize medal. His admirers talked then of running him for the next governor, but he traveled to Australia for a boxing tour instead, comi...\n\nQ: Sullivan held the world's heavyweight title for   _  .", "options": ["at least seven years", "only a year", "five years", "twenty-one years"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2143, "question": "Skin - diving is a new sport today. This sport takes you into a wonderful new world. It is like a visit to the moon. When you are under water, it is easy for you to climb big rocks because you are no longer heavy .Here, under water, everything is blue and green. During the day, there is plenty of light. When fish swim nearby, you can catch them with your hands.When you have tanks of air on your back, you can stay in deep water for a long time. But you must be careful when you dive in deep water. To catch fish is one of the most interesting parts of this sport. Besides, there are more uses for skin - diving. You can clean ships without taking them out of water. You can get many things from the deep sea. Now you see that skin -diving is both useful and interesting....\n\nQ: You can climb big rocks under water easily because  _  .", "options": ["you are very heavy", "you are as heavy as on the land", "you are not as heavy as on the land", "you have no weight at all"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1059, "question": "In recent years many countries of the world have been faced with the problem of how to make their workers more productive. Some experts claim the answer is to make jobs more varied. But do more various jobs lead to greater productivity? There is evidence to suggest that while variety certainly makes the worker's life more enjoyable, it does not actually make him work harder. As far as increasing productivity is concerned, then variety is not an important factor. Other experts feel that giving the worker freedom to do his job in his own way is important, and there is no doubt that this is true. The problem is that this kind of freedom cannot easily be given in the modern factory with its complicated machinery which must be used in a fixed way. Thus while freedom of choice may be important, ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the best way to make workers work harder according to the author?", "options": ["Increasing their pay.", "Giving them more spare time.", "Making the work itself meaningful.", "Replacing large production lines with small ones."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1705, "question": "Dear Mr. King, Your grocery store is outstanding in many ways. I enjoy the selection of produce and fresh bakery items. I have been a long time Supermart shopper and hope to continue for many years. I have found, however, that I must make a separate shopping trip to one of your competitors because there are many items your store does not carry. This becomes inconvenient for me, as my time is valuable, and I do not like to make two trips. Your low prices and excellent customer service keep me coming back to Supermart, but I would be a more satisfied customer if I could find all the items I need in one place. Specifically, I have never been able to purchase nacho cheese soup at your store. I can find other flavors of soup, but your store does not carry nacho cheese soup, a common ingredient ...\n\nQ: According to Bob, the grocery store   _  .", "options": ["meets all his needs", "is outstanding in every way", "offers good customer service", "lacks convenient transportation"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2823, "question": "Martha had been working for Miller Laboratories for two years, but she was not happy there. Nothing significant had happened in the way of promotions or salary increases. Martha felt that her supervisor, a younger and less experienced person than she, did not like her. In fact, the supervisor often said unpleasant things to her. One day, while talking with her friend Maria, she mentioned how discouraged she was. Maria gave her the name of a cousin of hers who was director of Human Resources Department for a large chemical company. Martha called him the next day and set up an interview on her lunch hour. During the interview, Mr. Petri said, \"You're just the kind of person we need here. You're being wasted in your other job. Give me a call in a day or two. I'm sure we can find a place for y...\n\nQ: Which of the following statement is NOT true?", "options": ["At her supervisor's criticism, Martha lost her temper.", "Mr. Petri felt Martha was not valued in her present job.", "Martha's interview with the director was on her lunch hour.", "Martha got the name of the director through her cousin."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 283, "question": "Chinese New Year celebrations, also known as the Spring Festival start on the 23rd day of the 12th lunar month of the Chinese calendar, and end on the 15th day of the first lunar month in the following year in the Chinese calendar. Chinese New Year's Day's date is calculated according to the Chinese lunar calendar. In 2015 it's Thursday, February 19. Many people clean their homes to welcome the Spring Festival. They put up the red posters with poetic verses on it to their doors, Chinese New Year pictures on their walls, and decorate their homes with red lanterns. It is also a time to reunite with s so many people visit their families at this time of the year. In the evening of the Spring Festival Eve, many people set off fireworks and firecrackers, hoping to cast away any bad luck and brin...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that", "options": ["the New Year symbols mean good for the future", "giving lucky money is a must for parents", "the Chinese celebrate the festival differently", "the staff in banks have a seven-day holiday"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3315, "question": "In the past ten years, America's National Basketball Association (NBA) has grown increasingly dependent on the rest of the world to supply players. When Michael Jordan and Larry Bird won gold in Barcelona in 1992, the Americans were praised for teaching the world how to play basketball. This season, however, 20 percent of NBA rosters will be filled by non-Americans. NBA commissioner David Stem happily embraces the trend. On a visit to Paris in October, Stern outlined his vision for the future, which is likely to see Europe hosting NBA games by 2010. The NBA is now planning to _ . \"Our experience in China has been that it is going to be explosive in its growth,\"said Stem. The strategy (,)in China is television.\"We've made 14 deals in China with local and national networks on cable and satel...\n\nQ: According to the report,  _  .", "options": ["Michael Jordan is still playing a very important role in NBA", "the part played by the foreign players in NBA will be great", "Yao Ming is to play two pre-season games in NBA", "European countries will host the 2004 NBA games"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1748, "question": "Where is that noise coming from? Not sure? Try living with your eyes closed for a few years. Blind people are better at locating sounds than people who can see, a new study says, without the benefits of vision the ears seem to work much better. Previous studies have shown that blind people are better than others at reaching out and touching the sources of sounds that are close by. Researchers from the University of Montreal wanted to see if blind people were also better at locating sounds that are far away. Twenty-three blind people participated in the study. All had been sightless for at least 20 years. Fourteen of them had lost their vision before age 11. the rest went blind after age 16. The experiment also included 10 people who could see but were wearing blind-folds. In one task, volu...\n\nQ: Which would be a proper title for the passage?", "options": ["A Research on Blind People", "Where is That Noise Coming from?", "Hearing Better in the Dark", "What If Living Without Your Eyes?"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3322, "question": "Phyllis Lee of prefix = st1 /Singaporeknew something wasn't right. Her younger son, Alex, then six years old, was getting good grades in his private kindergarten classes. But Lee realized something was wrong when Alex came home one day, crying, with \"zeroes\" on his Chinese spelling test. Lee decided to investigate. According to Lee, the teacher would frequently describe Alex's Chinese writing as 'ghost writings' and made him a laughing stock in class instead of helping him out. Lee, 46, spent the next 12 months teaching Alex and still helps him when necessary. She not only taught him the formation of the Chinese words but also their origin so that he could understand better, often taking more than an hour to read a simple paragraph. Visits to the library and surfing the Internet kept her u...\n\nQ: Alex arrived home with tears because_.", "options": ["he failed in the Chinese exam", "his teacher punished him", "he didn't want to learn Chinese", "his classmates did him wrong"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 300, "question": "Some years ago on a hot summer day in south Florida a little boy decided to go for a swim in the old swimming hole behind his house.In a hurry to dive into the cool water, he ran out of the back door, leaving behind shoes, socks, and shirt as he went. He flew into the water, not realizing that as he swam toward the middle of the lake, a crocodile was swimming toward him.His mother in the house was looking out of the window and saw the two.In great fear, she ran toward the water, shouting to her son as loudly as she could.Hearing her voice, the little boy became alarmed and made a U-turn to swim to his mother.It was too late.Just as he reached her, the crocodile reached him.From the shore, the mother grabbed her little boy by the arms just as the crocodile snatched his legs.That began an in...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is true according to the text?", "options": ["A crocodile attacked him when the boy and his mother were swimming.", "The crocodile bit the arms of the boy when it reached him.", "There is always an interesting story behind every scar.", "It was the farmer who shot the crocodile."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1605, "question": "Security Services advise that there have been robberies reported in the East Oxford area, carried out by a group and involving threats of and showing of a knife.The victims have all been young males of student age and appearance who have been walking alone between 7 pm and the early hours of the morning.Some of the victims have been followed from the O2 and the Regal Hotel. The Crime Prevention Advisor offers the following advice: *If possible walk home in a group, not on your own.If someone tries to take something from you by force, it may be best to give it to them, this way it will avoid you getting injured. *If someone tries to follow you, make for a public place, such as a shop or a restaurant or walk towards other people.Make lots of noise and use your personal alarm to shock the per...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE according to the text?", "options": ["Call Thames Valley Police on 101 when reporting an emergency.", "The victims are all young students walking home alone at night.", "Better give what you take to robbers when robbed of something.", "Choose quiet short cuts and you'll avoid being robbed successfully."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2524, "question": "\"A good parent\" can be a confusing phrase. It is almost impossible for one person to be \"a good parent\" at all stages of a child's life. Some parents are at their best before their children begin to speak. Others are most successful before their children enter elementary school. Still others make their finest contribution to older children or teenagers. Every parent can understand one stage of a child's development better than another. It is hard for a person to possess superior capacities throughout the entire period of a child's growth. A mother might be \"a good parent\" from her baby's birth until it is three; that is the period when it needs her protection and loving care. Then the start of her child's independence might upset and alarm her, and she might then become less helpful for a ...\n\nQ: Parents of \"nuclear\" families sometimes feel at a loss because   _  .", "options": ["they believe that such a family prevents the healthy growth of a child's personality and talent", "they dislike the support that other family members give to their children", "they do not always have the help of other family members in child-raising", "they no longer regard grandparents, uncles and aunts as good educators of their children"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1578, "question": "On a hot summer day, a soft drink can really take away your thirst. At home, at school, in the park or at the movies---you can find one almost anywhere. Carbonated You can see bubbles in these! Of all soft drinks sold, about 75 percent are carbonated . But be careful, carbonated soft drinks have lots of sugar and caffeine . Caffeine is not very good for you in the summer because it takes water out of your body. And the sugar can make you overweight if you drink too much. Fruit juice There are different kinds of juice. One kind is made only from fresh fruit. This kind of fruit juice may not taste sweet enough for some people, but it is nutritious . Another kind of fruit juice tastes good but has lots of sugar in it. Many young people buy this kind because the advertisements are good. It is ...\n\nQ: Which two types of drinks may make you overweight?", "options": ["Carbonated and fruit juice.", "Energy drinks and sports drinks.", "Carbonated and energy drinks.", "Fruit juice and bottled water."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 855, "question": "The South Pole is a particular place on the earth.When people stand at the top of it looking around,they will find all directions face to north.No matter how they make their first step in which direction,they will always walk towards the north.That's to say,only north and south exist there,neither east nor west exists. At the top of the South Pole,any clock or watch keeps good time because all meridians join there.All kinds of local time are completely suitable there.It is even difficult to distinguish New Year's Eve from New Year's Day. The explorers and scientists from different countries always fix the time according to their own.Therefore the time by their watches was different when the people with different nationality gathered there. The Winter Solstice is an important festival at th...\n\nQ: The Winter Solstice is an important festival   _  .", "options": ["in the world", "at the South Pole", "at the North Pole", "in China"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 589, "question": "It's a fact that we all dream. Some dreams seem to last for hours, others only for seconds. Some of us have strange dreams, some have interesting dreams, and some of us have unpleasant dreams. Tests in the 1980s showed that these dreams occur within 90-minute cycles, each cycle made up of six stages. In the last stage people experience rapid eye movement, known as REM, and it is in this stage that dreaming takes place. Eighty percent of people who were woken during this sixth stage could easily remember their dreams. On the other hand, when during the first five stages (NREM), only seven percent could describe a dream. However, of these same people woken during the first five stages, 74% were able to remember thinking activity, although they would not call it a dream. NerysDee, who has wri...\n\nQ: According to the tests in the 1980s, dreaming takes place  _  .", "options": ["between each 90-minute cycle", "at any time during 90-minute cycles", "during the first five stages of 90-minute cycles", "in the last stage of 90-minute cycles"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1803, "question": "D The year is 2094. It has been announced that a comet is heading towards the Earth . Most of it will miss our planet , but two pieces will probably hit the southern half of the Earth . On 17 July , a piece four kilometers wide enters the Earth's atmosphere with a massive explosion . About half of the piece is destroyed , but the remaining part hits the South Atlantic at 200 times the speed of sound . The sea boils and a huge hole is made in the sea bed . Huge waves are created and spread outwards from the hole . The wall of water , a kilometer high , rushes towards southern Africa at 800 kilometers an hour . Cities on the African coast are totally destroyed and millions of people re drowned . Before the waves reach South America , the second piece of the comet lands in Argentina . Earthqu...\n\nQ: What is mainly described in the passage ?", "options": ["A historic discovery .", "An event of imagination", "A research on space .", "A scientific adventure ."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 816, "question": "What is a lifestyle and how is that different from a life? A lifestyle is about brand names and buying identity or fame. Lifestyle gives a false sense of peace and acceptability that comes from others recognizing what you've bought into (as well as bought). If your car, clothes, and home are expensive, you're sophisticated and stylish. If you have the right kind of job or go to the right social gatherings, then you receive the insincere approval of others. This means that your self-esteem is always at the mercy of others, with no appreciation of you as an individual. A life, on the other hand, is very different. A life is what you lead when you know what matters most to you. It is very simple and comes from being connected to what you know is important and being willing to put that first, ...\n\nQ: To make the change, we need to  _  .", "options": ["be directed from within", "be directed from outside", "be driven by social values", "be driven by others' opinions"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2542, "question": "Music for Humans and Humpback Whales As researchers conclude in Science, the love of music is not only a universal feature of the human species, but is also deeply fixed in complex structures of the human brain, and is far more ancient than previously suspected. In the articles that discuss the field of bio-musicology, the study of the biological basis for the creation and appreciation of music, researchers present various evidence to, show that music-making is at once an original human \"business\", and an art form with skillful performers throughout the animal kingdom. The new reports stress that humans hold no copyright on sound wisdom, and that a number of nonhuman animals produce what can rightly be called music, rather than random sound. Recent in-depth analyses of the songs sung by hu...\n\nQ: Which of the following shows the advanced musical ability in humpback whales?", "options": ["They can remember complex material.", "They can create pleasing patterns of music.", "They can make sounds like drums continuously.", "They can sing along with rhythms of western music."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2495, "question": "Sir, The majority(=Most) of your readers must have been surprised and shocked to read a letter from Mr.R.Hogg,published in last Wednesday's Herald.Mr.Hogg seems to think that his own convenience and that of motorists in general are the only things that matter in our city. I would have supported Mr.Hogg if he had just made suggestions to improve the situation.No doubt his problems would be partly solved if the local government built a multi-storey car park in the city center,instead of encouraging motorists to use public transport.All the same,judging from the tone of Mr.Hogg's letter,I suspect that motorists who are so careless of pedestrians' safety that they would rather park their ears on the pavement than hold up the traffic would probably be too lazy to use a multi-storey car park if ...\n\nQ: What Mr.A.Walker does want to make known in his letter is that  _  .", "options": ["the total pedestrian casualty rate has fallen", "careless parking may cause serious traffic accidents", "the convenience of motorists in general matters much", "the safety of pedestrians matters lithe"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3201, "question": "Climate change has been blamed for killer hurricanes, sea level rise, and drought, but a new report suggests the effects of climate change might hit the world's coffee supply. Up to 70 percent of the world's coffee supply could be threatened over the next 66 years, according to a new study by researchers at England's Royal Botanic Gardens. Nearly 100 percent of the world's Arabica coffee growing regions could become unsuitable for the plant by 2080, according to the study. Beans from Arabica coffee plants account for about 70 percent of the world's coffee, but the plant also has to be grown under strict weather conditions: they grow well at temperatures between 64 and 70 degrees Celsius, and are highly influenced by frost or temperatures higher than 73 degrees Celsius. With temperatures es...\n\nQ: What is the result if Arabica coffee has less production?", "options": ["Coffee will replace oil to be the first most-traded commodity.", "Coffee is likely to become less popular than before.", "Some countries will suffer great economic losses.", "Farmers will plant other crops instead of coffee."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1918, "question": "If you're among the millions of Americans packing their vacation bags for summer trips,don't forget,however, that as soon as you step off the plane,you're expected to follow that country's laws.We took a look at one of the top countries Americans are most likely to visit and what might happen if you got caught. prefix = st1 /Mexico Smoking marijuana:If police find you smoking a cigarette which contains marijuana,they will most likely _ you overnight and you will get a fine. Carrying a firearm:You might be able to walk around with a gun in Texas,but that isn't so in Mexico,so leave your gun behind.If you wish to go hunting in Mexico.you can apply for a gun permit but expect to be charged $5,000.If you are caught bringing a firearm,Mexican policeman may take away your car and arrest you.An a...\n\nQ: When the travelers are in Mexico,they should NOT_.", "options": ["smoke the cigarettes", "hunt the animals without the permit", "carry a gun even if you have permit", "drive more than 50 mph on the highway"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 771, "question": "Attitude is an internal state that influences the choices of personal action made by the individual . Some researchers consider that attitudes come from differences between beliefs and ideas; others believe that attitudes come from emotional states. Here, we focus on the effects of attitudes upon behavior, that is, upon the choices of action made by the individual. The kinds of actions taken by human beings are obviously influenced greatly by attitudes. Whether one listens to classical music or rock, whether one obeys the speed limit while driving, whether one encourages one's husband or wife to express his or her own ideas-all are influenced by attitudes. These internal states are acquired throughout life from situations one is faced with in the home, in the streets, and in the school. Of...\n\nQ: According to the passage, attitudes  _  .", "options": ["come from different situations in one's life", "are largely affected by one's behavior", "remain unchanged in one's daily life", "could be chosen according to one's will"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 866, "question": "Most people who live in Seattle, Washington, love their city. There is a never-ending flow of fun things to do. But, people who live there do not always enjoy the day-after-day absence of sunshine during the winter months. It is documented fact that sunshine (or lack of it) plays a major role in how each of us meets the day. It also affects how we perform at school or work. When people are derived of sunlight, they can develop seasonal affective disorder, which makes it difficult for them to feel happy or get things accomplished. No major city in the United States is more affected by the \"sunshine factor\" than Seattle. To fight drizzle and fog during the winter months, Steve Murphy created a business that is very popular among the locals. The Indoor Sun Shoppe is more than a little ray of ...\n\nQ: The Indoor Sun Shoppe   _  .", "options": ["attracts people from different parts of the whole country", "aims to create a humid and well-lit environment during winter months", "brings only a little ray of sunshine during the gray days of Seattle's winter", "offers variety of goods helping people overcome seasonal affective disorder"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3124, "question": "In the last 500 years nothing about people--not their clothes, ideas, or languages has changed as much as what they eat. Chocolate drink was first made from the seeds of the cacao tree by South American Indians. The Spanish introduced it to the rest of the world during the 1500s. And although it was very expensive, it quickly became popular, In London, shops where chocolate drinks were served became important places. Some still exist today. The potato is also from the New World. Around 1600, the Spanish brought it from Peru to Europe, where it soon was widely grown. Ireland became so dependent on it that thousands of Irish people starved when the crop failed during the years of 1845--1846, and thousands more were forced to go to live in America. There are many other foods that have travele...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following changed more than others?", "options": ["Clothes.", "Ideas.", "Languages.", "Foods."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1192, "question": "Certain plants and animals can survive under what seem like impossible conditions. Blind fish live freely under ocean depths that are ly dark and cold. Bacteria live at temperatures of 600 degF or a higher in places where the heat comes from the deep earth. One of the most remarkable achievements that we can observe directly is the ability of the plants and animals in the desert. In the Death Valley ,temperatures of 134 degF in the shade have been officially reported Yet lizards live there ,along with 600 species of plants, 30 species of mammals? and even fish. While the days are terribly hot, the nights are extremely cold. Temperatures can fall down by as much as 50 degF. Plants called xerophytes are perfectly adapted to the extremely dry conditions. These plants have survived by developi...\n\nQ: The prickly pear survives in the desert by  _  .", "options": ["shedding leaves in times of drought", "sending its roots down 60 feet", "spreading its roots wide", "storing water in itself"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2711, "question": "Without any previous notice, a documentary dominated headlines and social websites over the weekend. Under the Dome, a 103-minute documentary self-funded by former CCTV news anchor Chai Jing was released on video-sharing websites in China on Feb 28. It has rapidly pushed the public awareness about air pollution and encouraged people to join in efforts to make a difference. Chai, 39, said she started the work out of her \"personal clashes\" with smog after she gave birth to a daughter. \"I sealed tight all the windows. I started every day by checking the air pollution index,\" Chai said. Millions of other people are also doing the same. While they stop there, Chai goes deeper. \"I don't want to live in this way. 1 need to find out where the smog comes from and what on earth is going on.\" Over a ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following statements is true?", "options": ["The documentary was made by Chai jing , who works in CCTV now.", "The documentary dominated headlines and social websites soon after it was broadcast on TV.", "Chai started making the documentary after she gave birth to a daughter.", "Chai thinks that it is the burning of coal and oil that leads to air pollution in china."], "answer": 2}]